好，我先说 - 好
Okay. I'll go first. Um-- Okay.
其实，我们根本不用来
Let me say, uh, we don't really need to be here.
- 我们结婚已经5年了- 6年
See, we've been married five years.- Six.
- 5、6年了，这就好像给汽车做个年检
- Five, six years. And this is like a checkup for us.
有机会可以检查一下引擎
Um, a chance to poke around the engine...
- 换换机油,替换一两个密封条 - 没错
maybe change the oil,replace a seal or two.- Yeah.
很好，那我们开始吧
Very well then. Let's pop the hood.
从1分到10分，你们会给彼此之间的感情打几分？
On a scale of one to 1 0,how happy are you as a couple?
- 8分- 等一下
- Eight.- Wait.
10分代表非常愉快，1分代表非常痛苦，还是……？
Ten being perfectly happy and one being totally miserable?
- 凭直觉说 - 好
- Just respond instinctively.- Okay.
- 准备好了么？- 好了
- Ready? - Ready.
- 8分 - 8分
- Eight.- Eight.
你们多长时间做次爱？
How often do you have sex?
这道题我不懂
I don't understand the question.
我也糊涂了，也要打1到10分吗？
Yeah, I'm lost.Is this a 1-to-10 thing?
那1分是表示做得很少，还是根本不做了？
Like, is one very little,or is one nothing?
严格来讲
Because, you know...
0分才是根本不做了
tech-technically speaking...the zero would be nothing.
是的，我们不知道什么是1分，什么是10分
That's right. And if we don't know what one is-What's 10?
嗯，因为10分，天啊
- Yeah, 'cause 10 Oh, God.
- 永恒的 - 不屈不挠的
- Constant. Uh... - Unrelenting.
- 不停下来，我是说，就像… - 没什么可吃的
- N-Not stopping for, like.. I mean,just..- Nothing to eat.
就像抢劫
Like Sting.
抢劫也就是一天的活
Well, look at Sting's day job.
谁一周有60小时做这个呢？
Who else has 60 hours a week to put in the sack?
这不是1到10的游戏，这是基本问题
It's not a one-to-1 0 scenario. It's a basic question.
你们一周做爱几次？
How often do you have sex?
那就说说这个星期吧
How about this week?
- 周末也算吗？- 当然
- Including the weekend? - Sure.
说说你们是怎么认识的？
Describe how you first met.
- 那是在哥伦比亚 - 博格达
Uh, it was- It was in Colombia.- Bogota.
-5年前 -是6年
- Five years ago. - Six.
好吧，5、6年前
Right.Five or six years ago.
不，不是，没事
No, no, no, no.Esta bien.
我们俩是一起的 放松
She's with me.Esta bien.
我叫珍妮
I'm Jane.
- 我叫约翰 - 很高兴认识你
- John.- Nice to meet you.
我也一样
Nice to meet ya.
- 为了虎口脱险 - 干杯
- To dodging bullets.- To dodging bullets.
话说完了
So, it speaks.
跳个舞怎么样？
But does it dance?
嗨，陌生人
Hiya, stranger.
我回来了
Hiya back.
没有客房服务
I think room service fled.
我尽力了
I did what I could.
谢谢
Thank you.
嗯，味道真不错
Mm! Oh, that's good.
希望如此, 我可是找了只羊挤的
I hope so. I had to milk a goat to get it.
女士们，先生们，碰碰运气吧
Ladies and gentlemen,try your luck
嘿 过来瞧瞧啊
Hey.! Step right up.!
嗨，这位女士，想试试么？有奖品哦
How about you, little lady? Wanna try your luck?Win a prize.
好啊
Hmm. Yeah.All right.
- 两位 - 欢迎两位
- Two.- We got two over here.
- 你知道怎么握枪么？
- Do you know how to hold it?
来瞧瞧啦 ……五美元一次，五美元
Step right up! Five shots. Five dollars.
- 这样？- 对
- Yeah. - Yeah?
对
Yeah
- 你必须先瞄准 - 我瞄准了
- You gotta aim. - I am.
别笑，我能杀了你的
Don't laugh. I'll kill you.
你没有瞄准
You didn't blink.
想给你的小女孩赢得一个小动物玩具吗
Would you like to win a stuffed animal for your little girl?
- 拜托 - 哦
- Come on. -  Ooh.
每个人都能赢
Everybody's a winner.
有奖品么？
Do we still get somethin'?
新手运气好
Beginner's luck.
- 我想要再打一次 - 那就再打一次
- I wanna go again.- We're goin' again.
大家都能赢 有奖品了 有奖品了
Everybody's a winner.Win a prize. Win a prize.
你在哪儿学的射击？
Where'd you learn to shoot like that?
新手运气好
Beginner's luck.
行了，行了，你才刚认识她6个星期！
Stop. Stop. You've only known the girl for six weeks.
我爱上她了，她聪明、性感
I'm in love.She's smart, sexy.
不羁、自然、有内涵
She's uninhibited,spontaneous, complicated.
是我见过的最美妙的女子
She's the sweetest thing I've ever seen.!
我认识格拉蒂丝两年半以后才向她求婚的
I knew Gladys for two and a half years before I asked her to marry me.
婚姻需要以相互了解为基础，不然的话, 很容易破裂的
You have to have a foundation of friendship,brother. The other stuff fades.
嗨
Hi.
你不认为这太快了吗？
So,you don't think this is all happening a little fast?
你知道我做事从来都是经过深思熟虑的
You know me. I never do anything without thinking it through.
他是干什么的？
What does he do?
他是搞建筑的，有名的承包商
He's in construction.He's a big-time contractor.
只要华尔街上哪台服务器坏了
A server goes down on Wall Street...
无论何时何地，她总是会及时出现
she's there anytime,day or night.
就像电脑界的蝙蝠侠
She's like Batman for computers.
他的性格和我也很像，简直是天生一对
He's gone as much as I am,so... it's perfect.
依我看，你们俩最多也就坚持六个月
I give the whole thing six months tops.
埃迪 我已经向她求婚了
Eddie, I asked her to marry me.
什么？
What?
- 我要结婚了！ - 我听不清
- I'm getting married. - What? I can't hear you.
- 结婚！- 我听不清
- I'm getting married.- I can't hear him.
别打他了，他刚才说什么疯狂的话了？
Can you stop hittin' him? I think he said somethin' crazy.
我要结婚了！
I'm getting married!
- 这水龙头该换了 - 嗯
- Gotta get these filters changed.- Mm-hmm.
你看维克斯勒大夫怎么样
What did you think of Dr. Wexler?
他的问题有些不知所谓
His questions were a bit wishy-washy.
是啊，小心手臂，不是很有见地
Yeah. Sorry.Not the most insightful.
他的办公室在城市另一边
His office is clear across town.
你知道4点钟是交通高峰期，我可不是很想去
You know that 4:00 means we hit rush hour.I'm not crazy about that.
- 就这么定了? - 好
- So, that's settled then, yeah? - Okay.
好
Okay.
晚饭7点钟
Dinner's at 7:00.
我会赶回来的
Yep. I'll be there- here.
- 亲爱的 - 时间正好
- Hi, baby.- Perfect timing.
外面下好大的雨
It's pissin' rain out there.
给你奶油 我买的
Here's your butter.I bring you butter.
- 工作怎么样？- 老样子
- How was work?- Eh, so-so.
我路上和艾迪喝了一杯
Oh, I stopped off for a drink with Eddie.
- 这是加了盐的 - 什么？
- This is salted.- What?
这是加了盐的
It's salted.
还有别的样子的吗？
Is there any other kind?
不加盐的
Unsalted.
就像我要的那种
Like I asked for.
没什么，我凑合用吧
It's fine. I'll make it work.
我买了新窗帘
Oh, I got new curtains.
你看怎么样？
Well?What do you think?
呃
Huh.
还有一个矮个子男人也想买这个窗帘，我们争了好半天
There was a struggle over the material.- This little tea sandwich of a man
是他先看到的 但最后还是我赢了
- He got his hands on them first, but I won.
当然
Of course you did.
新窗帘偏绿，沙发和地毯都需要换一下才相衬
They're a bit green. I think we're gonna have to reupholster the sofas...
我想换条波斯地毯，你看呢？
and definitely get a new rug,maybe a Persian.
要不就还用原来的，这样就什么都不用换了
Or we can keep the old ones.Then we don't have to change a thing.
我们不是已经谈过这件事儿了吗？记得么
We talked about this.You remember?
我记得我们说要先等一等的
I remember. I remember 'cause we said we'd wait.
如果你不喜欢，我就去退掉
If you don't like 'em,we can take 'em back.
好吧，我不喜欢
Okay. I don't like 'em.
你会慢慢习惯的
You'll get used to 'em.
我喜欢
I like 'em.
(信用卡)免年息，促销到3月份为止
Huh. Zero percent A.P.R. till March.
现在我们开始第二阶段
So, part two. Here we are.
只不过这次你是一个人来的，这是为什么呢？
Only this time,you came back alone.Why did you come back?
我也不清楚
I'm not sure really.
我先声明，我爱我妻子
Let me clarify.I love my wife.
我希望她幸福
Um, I want her to be happy.
我希望她一切顺利
Uh, I want good things for her.
但有时候，我……
But there are times...
- 亲爱的，你能不能……- 再看5分钟
- Honey, would you just...- Five more minutes.
那么问题是什么
So what's the problem?
我们之间存在着巨大的距离
There's this huge space between us...
因为有很多事情，我们都不告诉对方
and it just keeps filling up with everything that we don't say to each other.
- 这叫什么来着? - 婚姻
- What is that called? - Marriage.
你们不告诉对方的是些什么事情呢？
What don't you sayto each other?
呃
Uh- Hmm.
看上去不错嘛，新菜式？
This looks nice.Did you do something new?
- 嗯 - 是吗？
- Mm-hmm.- Yeah?
- 我加了豌豆 - 对，豌豆
I added peas. - Yeah, peas.
对，绿色的
Yeah, it's the green.
亲爱的，把盐递过来一下好吗？
Sweetheart, will you pass the salt?
不是在桌子中间么
It's in the middle of the table.
在桌子中间？
Oh, is that the middle of the table?
对，就在你我中间
Yeah. It's between you and me.
好吧
Okay.
- 你对他有多诚实？- 相当诚实
- How honest are you with him?- Pretty honest.
我是说……
I mean....
我从不对他说谎，只不过……
it's not like I lie to him... or anything.
有些小秘密，每个人都有小秘密啊
We just, uh, have little secrets.Everybody has secrets, you know.
对不起，亲爱的，我在找……
Shit. Sorry, honey.
- 我来收拾 - 不，还是我来吧，我来，你别动
- I'll get it.- No, I got it. I got it. Don't move.
对，是我
Oh, that's me.
- 天啊！亲爱的，你吓着我了- 对不起，亲爱的
- Jesus! Honey, you scared me.- I'm sorry, hon.
我正在找...你要出去么
I was lookin' for the, uh You goin' out?
对，城里不知道什么地方有个傻瓜弄坏了律师事务所的服务器，
Yeah. Some clown crashed a server in a law firm downtown...
所以我必须去一趟
and ended the world as they know it, so, yes.
嗯
Mmm.
我们答应要去科尔曼家的
We promised the Colemans.
- 我知道 - 好
- I know. - Okay.
我会去的，很快就能搞定
I'll be there. In and out.Just a quickie.
你也许会觉得只有你有这些问题
It probably feels like you're the only people going through this.
但我告诉你，成千上万的家庭....
But I'll tell you something.There are millions of couples...
都存在这些问题
that are experiencing the same problems.
是的
Uh-huh.
- 一小时后，我们要坐飞机走 - 好的
- We got a plane in an hour.- All right.
- 40 - 好，我跟……
- Forty. - I'll match your
靠，你是干什么的？
What the hell? What's this shite?
对不起，厕所在哪里？
Sorry. Where's the can around here For Chrissakes.
你们在玩扑克吗？
Hey, you guys playin' poker?
我们自己玩的，你给我滚
Private game. Piss off.
我可以一起来吗？我加进来怎么样
Hey, could I sit in? You think I can sit in?
你难道听不明白“你给我滚”？
What part of""piss off'do you not understand?
哥们儿，别这么凶嘛，
Guys. Hey, whoa, whoa.Be a little friendly.
我有钱……我有...
- I got the cash. I got the ca-
哇，我只是给你看我的钱包
Dude, I'm just showing you my bankroll, man.
我带了钱的
I got the money.
听到我说的了么？
You know what I'm saying?
有人感兴趣么
Poker- Don't even know her.
如果你们让我坐下的话，我就坐下
So if you want me to sit in, I'll sit in.
然后咱们来看看运气如何，如果你们不想赢钱，那我就走
And I'll play some cards with youse.If you don't, I won't.
我只想玩两手而已
I just Fine with me, I'll go.
上帝！- 这张椅子空着，我可以坐下来……
-Jesus.- Here's an empty chair.I could sit right here.
这是好运的位子
That is Lucky's chair.
好运在哪？我怎么看不到好运
Wh-Where's Lucky? I don't see Lucky.
- 好运还没回来呢 - 那我就先坐这里
- Lucky's not back yet. - Then I'll sit here.
除非……你们怕输给我
Unless... I'm too hot for ya.
- 纯银的 - 哦，不错啊
- Solid silver.- Ooh. Raise the socks.
“虎口脱险，爱你的珍妮”
""To dodging bullets. Love,Jane.''
放在桌子上，放上去
In the pot. Put it in the pot.
喔，他赢了
Oh, he's pulled something.
你们有麻烦啦
- He's pulled something.- You're in trouble now.
- 60块，对吧？- 赚了！
- Sixty dollars, eh? - In!
接着来玩牌吧！
Let's play some poker.!
- 5点 - 他连输了14把
- Drat! - You've got 1 4 different tells.
你的运气真是背到家了
- You are bleeding William Tell.
- 这他妈的是怎么回事？- 对不起，好运
- What the hell is this? - Sorry, Lucky.
你该走了，朋友，和你玩牌很开心
- Looks like you're done, pal.Thanks for the memories.
你就是好运？
Oh, you Lucky?
- 是的 - 别开玩笑了
- Yeah. - No kiddin'.
你是什么人？找活儿干的吗？
What is it, kid? You lookin' for a job or somethin'?
你就是我的活儿
- You are the job.
一对三
Pair of threes.
- 你是个坏男孩吗 - 是的
- Have you been a bad boy? - Yes.
嗯？
- Mm-hmm?
你知道我会怎么对待坏男孩吗？
You know what happens to bad boys?
- 我会惩罚他们 - 哦，惩罚我吧
- They get punished.- Oh,yeah. Punish me.
你是不是把军火卖给坏家伙了？
Have you been selling big guns to bad people?
瑞西先生？
Mr. Racin.
瑞西先生？你没事吧？
Mr. Racin. You okay?
哦，要去科尔曼家
Oh, Colemans.
他出事了！
He's down.!
在沙发上
On the sofa!
计程车
Taxi.
- 工作顺利吗？- 是的，这边
- Everything okay at work? - Yeah. Here.
- 是吗？- 你呢？比赛怎么样？
- Yeah?- And you? How was the game?
- 很精彩 - 不错
- The game was good.- Good.
网队加时赛赢了
Nets in overtime.
- 你喝酒了？- 你说对了，小姐
- You been drinking? - That's right, miss.
欢迎，邻居们！
Welcome, neighbors.!
- 嗨，苏珊 - 你好，约翰
- Hey. Hi, Susan.- Good to see you,John.
- 这是给你们的 - 哦，太棒了
- There you go.- Oh, this is wonderful.
谢谢
Thank you.
哦，我喜欢这个
Oh, I love that.
- 这衣服真好看 - 谢谢，你的也是
- What a lovely dress.- Thank you very much. So is yours.
- 来，我来给你介绍几个姐妹 - 别玩太疯了
Come on. Let's go see the girls.Don't stray too far,guys.
你想来支古巴雪茄吗？
You want a Cuban?
不，我不抽烟
Oh, no, no, no. I don't smoke.
- 干净的身体，清洁的灵魂，苏珊总这么说 - 没错
-  Oh.Clean body, clean soul.That's what Suzy says. - Ain't that the truth?
- 你什么恶习都没有么？- 多多少少有点
- You guys have any vices? - Well, you know.
- 你要喝点什么吗？- 夏敦埃（白葡萄酒），谢谢
- Can I get you a drink? - Uh, yes. Chardonnay, please.
- 你们呢？- 一样
- Girls? - Chardonnay.
- 爸爸，爸爸，爸爸 - 我去喝一杯
- Daddy, Daddy, Daddy! - I'll be up here at the filling station.
道氏股不会再走高 说是越来越糟
Duxbury's never gonna close that high. I hear their stock's getting butchered.
嘿 约翰
Hey,John.
日子不好过啊
It's a bloodbath over there.
上个季度你赚了多少？有没有受到影响？
Johnno. How'd you make out last quarter? You take a beating?
实际上，我把所有的钱都埋在杂物间下面了
Actually, I got all my dough buried under the toolshed.
- 我老公刚升职了- 哦，天哪，真不错！
- So, Chuck got the promotion. - My God.! That is so great.!
太激动了，我们终于可以把厨房重新装修一下了
I'm so excited. We can finally put the addition on the kitchen.
喔，又来了 (孩子吐了)
Oh, shit. Not again.
我应该穿件雨衣
I should wear a raincoat.
你能帮我抱一下吗？
You know what? Would...Can you hold her for a second?
- 什么？不，我真的不行  - 它弄得到处都是
- What? No. I'd rather not. - It's all over the applique.
- 不，我…… - 请帮帮忙
- Oh, no, I'm.... - Please,just-
好吧
ok
我得去洗洗
Oh. Seltzer.
啊，她喜欢你
Oh, she likes you.
我喜欢你今晚穿的衣服
I liked your dress tonight.
很漂亮
It was nice.
谢谢
Thank you.
- 早上到那边，好 - 当然
- Be there in the morning. Okay.- Of course.
- 有什么事吗？- 没，没事，是爸爸打来的
- Everything all right?- Uh, yeah. It was- It was Dad.
他以为得了肺炎
He's a....He thinks he has pneumonia.
我估计是着凉了，你知道他就那样，会没事的
I'm sure it's just a cold,and you know how he is. He'll be fine.
应该会吧
Yeah. Probably.
也许你得去看看他，他会高兴的
Maybe you should go see him.I think he'd like that.
是的,嗯，有空会去的
Hmm. Yeah.Yeah, maybe I will.
晚安
Good night then.
- 你那是谁打来的？- 嗯？
- Who was that? - Huh?
- 谁刚才打电话来？ - 哦，亚特兰大那边的办公室
- Who was on the phone? - Oh, the Atlanta office.
大坝又出了点问题
There's a problem with the specs for the dam again.
我明早飞过去，在那待两天
I'll fly in the morning.I'll be gone a couple of days.
- 该死的大坝 - 嗯，真该死
- That damn dam, huh? - Yup, that damn dam.
- 好吧，晚安，约翰 - 晚安
- All right, good night,John. - Good night.
好
Okay.
早上好，史密斯先生，亚特兰大又有麻烦了- 我听说了
- There's trouble in Atlanta again.- That's what I hear.
有什么要给我的？- 登机牌，计程车收据……
- What you got?- I've got your boarding pass and taxi receipts.
把口香糖吐出来 - 你有纸巾么？
- Get rid of that gun-gum. - You got a tissue?
- 还有你的旅馆帐单，别丟了 - 谢谢
- And your hotel bill. Now don't lose those. - Thanks.
门没锁
The door's unlocked.
早上好，伙计
Morning, pal.
- 你怎么样？- 还那样 杀不完的人
- How you doin'? - Same old same old. People need killin'.
这周末在我家有个聚会
Oh,Johnny. I might have a little get-together this weekend... at my house.
烤肉，没有女人，只有大老爷们，很爽的
Barbecue. No ladies. Dudes only. It's gonna be awesome.
- 嗯，我回头和我老婆说一声 - 你要用我手机吗？
- Yeah. I'll talk to the missus. - You wanna use my cell phone?
也许你要擦屁股时也得给她打电话
Maybe you wanna give her a call in case you wanna decide to scratch your ass...
或者回头报告，确保她同样
or use the head later,make sure she thinks it's okay.
你和你妈住一块
You live with your mother.
你总向她报告干什么？她像是第一夫人
Why would you bring her into this? She happens to be a first-class lady.
我不是什么事都向她报告
I don't have to check in with her every time I wanna do somethin'.
她做饭，打扫，给我弄吃的
She cooks, cleans,makes me snacks.
我是聋子？
I'm the dumb guy?
约翰·史密斯
John Smith.
- 你好，约翰 - 早，亚特兰大
- Hello,John. - Good morning, Atlanta.
这星期有很多目标
Quite the body count this week.
其中有一个最重要，我们需要你来完成
We have a priority one,so I need your expertise.
目标的名字叫本杰明·丹兹，绰号坦克
The target's name is Benjamin Danz,A.K.A. ""the Tank.''
他对公司有很大威胁，受到DIA的严密保护
He's a direct threat to the firm.D.I.A. custody.
国防情报局准备在墨西哥边界以北15公里处用直升机进行地空转运
They're making a ground-to-air handoff to heli...1 0 miles north of the Mexican border.
一定不能让他们顺利交接
I need you to make sure the target does not change hands.
“坦克”？
The Tank?
- 埃坦科技……- 确认是珍妮·史密斯
- I-Temp Technology Staffing.-  Jane Smith confirmed.
准备放行
Stand by for contact.
对不起，打扰了，有重要情况
Sorry to interrupt, but we have a situation.
对手总想消灭我们
You know the competition would love to see us burn...
这次需要你亲自出马
so I need you to handle this personally.
- 目标？ - 本杰明·丹兹
- Target? - Benjamin Danz.
资料马上传给你，
I'm rolling the specs now.
这次一定要干净利索
We need this quick, clean and contained.
好的，先生
Yes, sir.
- 早上好，女士们 - 早上好
- Good morning, ladies. - Good morning.
- 你好，珍妮
- Hello,Jane.
昨天的行动死了一个，还有一个被拘留
Yesterday's op resulted in one kill and one agent in protective custody.
明天再保他出来
Not good.We'll get him out tomorrow.
两箱G-40送来了 还有榴弹发射器
Another two cases of the G40's. The grenade launchers are here.
再要十箱
Order 1 0 more.
好，开始吧，杰丝
All right. Go,Jas.
目标的名字叫本杰明·丹兹，绰号“坦克”
The target's name is Benjamin Danz, A.K.A. ""the Tank.''
- 你肯定吗？- 是的
- Are you serious? - Yeah.
目标将穿过边界，被护送到某个联邦机构
The target's being moved across the border to a federal facility.
唯一可以动手的地方在边界南面
The only point of vulnerability is just south of the border.
我要当地的GPS和SAC数据
I want G.P.S. and S.A.C. of the canyon...
还有最近三天的天气报告
and the weather report for the last three days.
目标会在一个废弃的跑道上转乘直升机，
Target will rendezvous with the helicopter here at a deserted airstrip.
那里是我们唯一的机会
We will have one chance to strike.
- 准备好了么？- 一切就绪，四周炸药埋设完毕
- Are we green? - Perimeter is armed. We are up and running.
红色，红队，这是蓝队，
Red team.! Red team.!This is BroadwayJoe.
我们正在进入指定区域
Halftime is approaching
收到，蓝队
Copy that, BroadwayJoe
喔，天啊
Oh, come on.
- 你看见了么？- 看到，对我们有威胁吗？
- You getting this?-  Affirmative. Is it a threat?
倒记时开始了，卡车还没有进入引爆区域
Countdown's initiated.Convoy is not in the zone yet.
有个傻瓜闯了进来，会引爆炸弹的
There's an idiot in the field.He's gonna blow the charges.
好吧
Okay.
开什么玩笑！
You gotta be kidding.
平民
Civilians.
让我们看看这玩意儿的威力
Let's see if we can't get a tune out of this trombone.
发现武器
We're picking up a weapon signature.
糟糕，不是平民
Shit! Not a civilian.
嘿，真是的
Oh, man.
混蛋
Asshole.
目标进入区域 倒计数开始
Convoy is in the zone!Countdown is initiated.
哇哦
Whoa!
这东西没买错
You should so not be allowed to buy these things.
放弃！放弃！
Abort.! Abort.!
我想我打中他了
I think I got I.D'd on that hit.
我想我可能被认出来了，你有没有被认出来过？- 没有
- You ever been I.D.'d on a hit?- Not that I'm aware of, no.
- 好吧 看来我有麻烦了 - 你看到他了么？
- Right. I think I'm in trouble.- You get a look at 'im?
小个子 大约十到十五英尺高
Little thing. Buck 1 0, buck 1 5 tops.
- 也许是菲律宾人 - 可能
- Maybe he's Filipino. - Maybe.
可能不一定是个男的
I'm not even sure it was a him.
你是说你被一个女的教训了？
Are you sayin' that you got your ass kicked by some girl?
我想是的，而且是个职业的  -真的吗
- That's right.A pro. - Really?
那应该不难查到
This should be easy.
我的意思是 这行总共才有多少女的呢 是吧
I mean, how many hitters do you know that are chicks? Right?
对不起 哥们
I'm sorry, man.
- 你们还要来点甜点吗？- 有什么呢，宝贝？
- You guys want any dessert?- What do you have, honey?
- 冰淇凌 - 冰欺凌？
- Ice cream.- Ice cream?
听起来不错，有什么味儿的
- That sounds delicious. What flavors do you have?
巧克力的和香草的
- Chocolate and vanilla.
两种我都不喜欢
I don't like either of those...separately.
不过放在一起的话可能不错
But maybe mixed together,that could be... a nice little dish.
你懂我的意思？而且别光是一小杯
You know what I mean? And not just a little pink spoon.
我要个大的圣代
I'd like the whole sundae.
- 可以办到 - 太好了
- That could be arranged. - Perfect.
“可以办到”，你听听那口气，看来她对我有意思
Could be arranged. Did you hear that? I'd like to have her kick my ass.
- 你知道我的意思吧 - 嗯
- You know what I mean? - Right.
除了体重之外还有其他的线索么？
Did you get any other details on her besides her weight class?
笔记本电脑
- Laptop.- I'm sorry? You're in a whole zone right now.
我没听清楚你说什么
I'm havin' a hard time talkin' to you.
- 笔记本电脑 - 笔记本电脑，好
- Laptop. - Okay, laptop.
我要知道那个混蛋是谁
I wanna know who that bitch is!
- 把录像带给我 把带子给我 - 珍妮
- Get me that tape. -Jane.
把录像带给我
Get me that tape
- 怎么了？ - 老板的电话
- What? - It's Father.
FBI放弃了交接，行动失败了
The F.B.I. secured the package.The window's closed, sir.
我告诉过你不允许有任何闪失
I told you we couldn't afford any mistakes on this one.
- 还有另外一个杀手 - 我们不能留下任何活口
- There was another player.- We do not leave witnesses.
如果那个杀手认出你，你是知道规矩的
If this player I.D. 'd you You know the rules.
我给你48小时，珍妮
You have 48 hours to clean the scene,Jane.
我会办妥的，先生
Lookin' forward to it, sir.
好，我们有新目标了，我们来查查他是谁
All right. We have a new target.Let's find out who he is.
天啊，怎么搞成这样？
Jesus.What did you do to it?
在火里烤过？
Put a campfire out with it?
买个新的吧
Buy a new one.
它的主人对它很有感情
This one has sentimental value for its owner.
是谁的？
Who's that?
我正是希望你能告诉我，格温
Well, Gwen,I'm just hoping you'd tell me.
你为什么这么急着想知道？
So, uh, why you gotta know so bad anyway?
你了解我 我只想物归原主
You know me.Just tryin'to return some lost property.
- 嗨，费尔 - 嗨，约翰
- Hey, Phil. - Hey,John.
- 你吃素？ - 不
- Are you a vegan? - No.
我女朋友吃素
My girlfriend is.
让我们看看
Here we go.
升级的内存模组
Upgraded RAM module.
芯片是中国产的 Dynamix进口的
Chip's Chinese.Imported by Dynamix.
零售商是……
Retailed by, uh-
也许能查到地址
You know, I might be able to get you a billing address.
好了
All right.
没有名字，只有地址
No name.Just an address.
莱克星顿大道570号，5003室
57 0 Lexington Avenue.Suite 5003.
纽约
New York.
你知道这个地址吗？
You know the place?
我靠……
SweetJesus.Mother of God.
你们俩去给我冲杯咖啡
Why don't you both go make some coffee?
珍妮，是你丈夫的电话
Jane, it's your husband.
他从亚特兰大回来了，问你晚饭怎么吃？
He's back from Atlanta.He wants to know about dinner.
告诉他，7点钟吃晚饭
Tell him...dinner's at 7:00.
嗨，约翰，她说7点钟吃晚饭
Hi,John. Yeah,she says dinner's at 7:00.
好，和往常一样
It always is.
很准时嘛
Perfect timing.
和往常一样
As always.
- 真是个惊喜 - 希望如此
- This is a nice surprise.- I hope so.
- 你比平常回来得早嘛 - 我很想你
- You're home early.- I missed you.
我也很想你
Mm. I missed you too.
- 吃饭吧 - 好啊
- Shall we? - Yes.
只有特别的日子才会这样
Thought you only broke these out for special occasions.
今天是个特别的日子
This is a special occasion.
炖肉，我最喜欢吃的
Mm! Pot roast.My favorite.
我来吧，宝贝
Allow me, sweetheart.
你累了一天了
You've been on your feet all day.
谢谢
Thank you.
不用
Sure.
工作怎么样？
So, how's work?
有件委托出了点问题
Actually, we had a little trouble with a commission.
- 没事吧？ - 没事
- Is that right? - Yeah.
我们和另外一家公司订重了
Double booking with another firm.
- 四季豆？- 不用, 谢谢
- Green beans?- No, thank you.
来点吧
You'll have some.
希望一切顺利
I hope everything works out okay.
目前还没有
It hasn't yet
不过会好的
but it will.
烤肉我最爱吃了
Pot roast is my favorite.
亲爱的，能把盐递给我么？
Sweetheart,could you pass the salt?
你用了什么新花样吗？- 嗯
- Did you try something new?- Mm-hmm.
亚特兰大怎么样？
So, how was Atlanta?
我们那边也有问题，数目对不上
Had a few problems ourselves.Some figures didn't add up.
- 严重吗？- 生死攸关
- Big deal?- Life or death.
来点葡萄酒？ - 好的
- Wine?- Yeah.
- 我来收拾吧 - 我去拿毛巾
- I got it. - I got it. I'll get a towel.
珍妮？
Janey?
宝贝？
Honey?
珍妮！
Jane!
我怎么这么笨！
How could I be so stupid?
珍妮！珍妮！
Jane.!Jane.!
珍妮！
Jane.!
喔，天啊！
God.
哦 天哪
Oh, dear God.
不，不，刚才不是故意的！那是意外
Wait. No, no, no, no.Accident.
宝贝，是个意外！
Honey? Accident.
珍妮，停车 马上
Jane, stop the car! Now!
珍妮？
Jane.!
你反应过度了
You've overreacting!
亲爱的 别这样好吗
Honey, let's not get carried away.
我不想让你生气，我们可以谈谈
We don't wanna go to sleep angry.
天哪！
God!
把车停下来
Pull over.
停车，停车！
Pull over.! Pull over.!
你听着……
Now, look
我们得谈谈！
We need to talk!
好了 来了 来了
Okay, I'm comin'. I'm comin'.
- 来了，是谁啊？- 开门
- Who is it? - Open up.
- 你怎么了？- 我老婆
- What the hell happened to you?- My wife.
- 她想杀了我 - 是吗，听我说
- She tried to kill me.- Yes, she did. And you know what?
我老婆也想杀了我，不过不是用车
Gladys tried to kill me, not with a car.
至少你老婆更直截了当
At leastJane was a man about it.She was up front about it.
事实上，她们都想杀了我们，
They all try to kill you- slowly, painfully, cripplingly.
一点一点地折磨你
And then-wham.They hurt you.
你知道我当初有多难受吗？我曾经自虐
You know how hurt I used to be over her,and I used to beat myself up?
现在好了 我成天都在交女朋友，
Now I'm great. I got dates all the time.
我醒悟了，我找回了自我
I just woke up from a thing.I'm in my robe.
- 你和你妈住在一起 - 我之所以这样
- You live with your mom. - I live with my mom because I choose to.
是因为她是我唯一可以信任的女人
Because that's the only woman I've ever trusted.
她们大部分是被动侵略性的
Most of them are passive-aggressive.
这是心理学，我读了书，得到了观点
There's a whole psychology.I've been reading books,given what I've gone through.
很恶心
And, uh, it's disgusting.
你知道吗，这地球上没什么比一个13岁女孩更凶残了
Do you know there is nothing more cruelon this Earth than a 1 3-year-old girl.
她们在高中就结成小圈子
They literally form cliques in high school.
她们还互相较劲，划清界线
And they play cruel games on each other.A-And test boundaries with each other.
- 你在说什么？
- What are you talking about?
在说你要明白的…
I'm just saying about you have to understand-
我在这受着伤，你却说13岁女孩
I'm hurting over here.And you're talking about 1 3-year-old girls.
因为我想帮你战胜疼痛
Because I'm trying to get you past the hurt.
你要了解你的敌人
You have to understand the enemy what you're up against.
我知道你在想什么
I know exactly what you're thinkin'.
她连这个都对你说谎，那还有什么不能骗你的呢？
If she lied about that, what else is it possible that she lied about?
她是个间谍，专门监视别人的行动
Her job is a spy to get information from people.
法国海滨，游艇，伊朗王子……
French Riviera, a yacht? An Iranian prince?
她用色相来套取情报，太恶心了
She's supposed to get close to him and gain his trust. It's disgusting.
什么？你说什么？
What?What are you saying?
什么？你丈夫是那个杀手？
What?Your husband is the shooter?
那不可能
That's impossible.
真的
Really?
也许这一开始就是一个布置好的局，专门监视你
This whole thing was probably planned from the beginning.
在你身边潜伏了6年，收集情报，
Operation Stake OutJohnny. A six-year stakeout to get information from you.
现在任务完成了
Mission accomplished.
好吧
Okay.
看开一点
Here's the upside.
- 你并不爱他 - 没错
- You don't love him. - No.
那就杀了他，你是最好的杀手
You'll kill him, and nobody's better at that than you are.
- 谢谢 - 然后一切就都结束了
- Thank you. - And then it'll be over.
- 如果她窃听怎么办？- 什么？
-  What if she's listening? - What?
你觉得她可能窃听这房子吗？
Do you think it's possible that she rigged the house?
- 哦，天啊 - 伙计
-Oh, my God. - Hey, dude.
很可能，因为她周围那群人
It could be very possible because of th-the pattern of how she's handled stuff.
我不奇怪，这也许是她不喜欢我的原因
It wouldn't surprise me. That's probably why she doesn't like me.
- 因为她听到我叫她侏儒 - 你疯了
- Because she heard me call her a troll. - You're out of your mind.
我说这是可能的，那女人要开车撞死你
I'm just saying it's possible. The woman just tried to run you over with a car-
她可能会听到
That she could hear you.
我才不管，我希望她在听
And I don't give a shit.I hope she is listening.
我希望你在听，珍妮，你知道吗，我在注意你
I hope you are listening,Jane.You know what, I'm on to you.
你也许在愚弄我的兄弟，因为他瞎了，没什么，她知道
You might have fooled my boy, 'cause he was blinded. It's okay. She knows this.
但是我不是我，我希望你在听
But I'm not me.I hope you're listening to me.
我希望你知道我曾和你朋友杰斯麦睡过觉
And I hope you know th-that I slept with your friend,Jasmine. Huh?
- 嘘 - 我们主动
- Shh.- We're on the board.
我们主动
I'm just saying we're on the board my man. Come on. We're on the board.
你以为是37比0，我们会得5分
You thought it was 37-0. We got five points on the board.
杰斯麦床上功夫很差的 约翰 我不是...
I nailed Jasmine and she was bad in bed, baby.Johnny, I'm not-
约翰，我知道你很尴尬，不过你放心，我埃迪不是别人
I know you're embarrassed, but, come on,it's me. It's Eddie you're talkin'to.
我不会和其他同事说的 我谁也不会说的
The guys we work with, they don't know.I'm never gonna tell them.
或许你老婆的同事可能因此在嘲笑她很长一段时间
The people she works with probably got a big laugh over this over the last six years.
但是又怎样呢 谁在乎 这并不重要
But so what? Who cares? That's not important.
听着，这就像一本已经写了150页的书
Lookit, it's like 1 50 pages of a book have been written.
前150页，约翰就是个大傻蛋
In the first 1 50 pages,Johnny's been a clown.
但你还可以写最后10页，虽然你被蒙骗了 但是你可以反败为胜
You can write the last 1 0 pages.You've been smoked,but you can write the last 1 0 pages.
能跟你这样谈谈心是我的荣幸，我们应该经常这么谈谈心
Great talk, man. We should do it more often. It was a great talk.
- 我借这个用用 - 我支持你
- I'm proud of you.- I'm gonna borrow this.
- 要不明天早晨再干吧- 行
- I like where your head's at.
- I'll do it in the morning.
- 你还好吗？- 好
- You okay?- Yep. Okay.
- 那好 晚安- 晚安
- Good night.- Good night.
你不爱他
You don't love him.
- 晚安，约翰- 晚安，埃迪
- Good night,John.- Good night, Eddie.
晚安，妈妈
- Good night, Mom.
姐妹们，开始吧
Okay, girls, let's go.
袋装垃圾，收据，火柴盒，你们都知道应该干些什么
Pocket litter, receipts, matchbooks.You know the drill.
很好 谁把这个翻出来了？
This is nice. Who picked this out?
- 这是什么？- 好像是你的婚礼
- What is this?- It looks like your wedding.
我知道，你们看这个干嘛？
I know what it is. What are you doing?
调查目标背景
Research. Background on the target.
这个房间不用查了，谢谢
This room is wrapped.Thank you.
不离不弃，相爱相惜，白头到老……
to have and to hold,to love and to cherish.Till death do us part.
我愿意
I promise.
我，约翰，愿意娶珍妮为妻……
I,John, take you,Jane, for my lawfully wedded wife...
永不分离
- to have and to hold-
所有东西都已经拿出来了
It's all coming out of the house.
好了 姑娘们 我们撤
Well done, ladies.Let's wrap it up.
怎么了，史密斯太太？庭院派对啊, 小妹妹
- What's going on, Mrs. Smith? - Garden party, girls.
嗨，邻居  - 嗨 约翰
- Hi, neighbor. -John, hey.
- 嘿 - 哦，南瓜，真大啊
- Hey.- Ooh, pumpkin. It's a big one.
喔，真不敢相信我从来没来过，看起来真不错
Wow. I can't believe I've never been in here before. This is great.
- 先看看客厅 - 噢，好
- Let's start with the living room. - Oh, yeah.
- 我好喜欢你家的地板，柚木的么？
- Oh. Nice floors. They teak or something?
- 也许，但愿我能知道 马丁
- Yeah.Fuck if I know, Martin.
你还赢得了今年高尔夫大师赛的冠军？
Uh, and you won the Golf Masters' trophy this year.
再次夺冠 明年就是你的了
Again. It'll be sittin' on your mantel next year.
婊子！
Bitch.
重点调查目标的履历
Target profile is our main priority.
必要时可以使用任何手段
Utilize all means necessary.
电话记录，信用卡，民用频率音频扫描
Phone taps, credit cards. Audio scan civilian frequencies.
用什么？珍妮
Uh, with what,Jane?
你好，这是史密斯家
You've reached the Smiths.
我们现在不能回复，请留下你的口信
We can't take your call right now,but leave a message after the tone...
我们会联系你的
and we'll get back to you.
- 查询数据库 - 找什么？约翰·史密斯？
- And search the database.- For what? John Smith?
- 一定要找到他 - 呃 珍妮？
- Find him. - Uh,Jane.
怎么了？
What?
- 我想我找到他了 - 在哪里？
- I think I found him. - Where?
就在我们这里
Here.
热传感器感应到有人接近
Heat sensor breach in the perimeter.
开始扫描所有楼层
Commence scanning all floors.
嗨，老公，我不是告诉过你不要来办公室找我么？
I thought I told you not to bother me at the office, honey.
- 你目前还是史密斯夫人 - 又不光我一个人叫史密斯夫人
- Well, you are still Mrs. Smith. - Well, so are a lot of girls.
小心点，珍妮，我随时可能进来干掉你们
Careful,Jane. I can push the button anytime, anywhere, sweetheart.
就是给你地图，你也找不到我们
Baby, you couldn't find the button with both hands and a map.
最后的警告，你还是逃吧
Last warning. You need to disappear.
- 不  - 现在
- no  - now
D区安全
""D'' Sector clear.
你想要我翻个身假装睡着了吗？
You really expect me to roll over and play dead?
我们结婚5年了，你应该习惯了
You should be used to it after five years of marriage.
是6年，我是不会逃走的
Six. And I'm not leaving.
"E"区安全
""E'' Sector clear.
嗯
Uh-huh.
随时随地
Anywhere, anytime.
发现入侵者
Intruder detected.
立即撤离，C计划
Evacuate. Plan ""C.''
正在撤离
Evacuation in progress.
这边已经搞定了
I've already done this side.
出发！
Let's go.!
胆小鬼！
Chickenshit!
孬种！
Pussy.!
你拿枪对着她，却没有开枪
You're tellin'me you had a shot at her and you didn't take it?
还给我带来这么多垃圾
What I'm trying to say is we got all this stuffhere...
你想说你搞不定她？
and you're trying to tell me you couldn't take her out?
现在她成了我们两个人的敌人，
Well, now she's a problem for both of us.
我家就是她的首要目标
Now my house is priority one.
来帮我一把，好吗？
Just give me a hand,will ya?
拜托 拿着个钳子对着个破炉子，你不疯我都要疯了
Please. You're driving me crazy with the tongs in the furnace.You're like an insane man.
好吧 他们给你48小时，
All right. They gave you 48 hours.
我们还剩下多少时间？
What do we got left here?
- 23？22？- 18个小时多一点
Twenty-three? Twenty-two? - Eighteen and change.
过了这18个小时你就完蛋了？
You got 18 hours until they close the book on both of you?
埃迪？
Eddie.
妈！我们处于高度戒备，
Mom! We're on high alert here!
刚才我差点就把你杀了
I almost killed you right then!
- 你还不知道！- 没事儿
You do not even realize! - Never mind.
这一切我受够了
I am so done playing games with this broad.
你应该照她头上来一枪
You gotta take this bitch out head-on.
不用你教我该怎么对付我老婆
Don't tell me how to handle my wife.
她不再是你老婆了，她是敌人，现在她也许就在外面
This broad is not your wife.She's the enemy. And she could be outside right now.!
埃迪
Eddie.
找到了
Got it.
很好，只剩下最后一步了
Now we're talkin'. Only question is how much is it to buy a vowel?
- 黑弓地产 - 你好，我是埃坦科技的
- Blackbow Realty. -  Yes. Hi. I'm calling from I-Temp.
太好了！我们的新居建得怎么样了
Oh, great.How's that new penthouse working out?
不错，多谢关心
Well,just fine.Thank you for asking.
我们是保安，你的电梯有问题，先生
This is security.There seems to be a problem with your elevator, sir.
你希望我们派个工程师来检查一下吗？
Do you want an engineer to come up and, uh, see what the problem is?
慢慢来，我在这里挺舒服的
Take your time.I'm really quite comfortable.
你真的挺舒服么？
Are you really comfortable?
珍妮？
Jane?
是你么，亲爱的？
Is that you, sweetheart?
第一次，也是最后一次警告，约翰，逃命吧
First and last warning,John. Get out of town.
你知道我哪里也不会去的
You know I'm not goin' anywhere.
别嘴硬了
Oh, well, so you say.
你现在陷在70层楼上的一个铁盒子里
But right now you're trapped in a steel box
你下面除了空气什么都没有
hanging 7 0 floors over nothin' but air.
喔，这原来是个陷阱
Oh, so this is a trap.
他在3号电梯
He's in car three.
这对我没用，宝贝
It's never gonna work, honey.
因为你总是低估我的能力
It's never gonna work because you constantly underestimate me.
- 是吗？- 你不知道我是谁
- Do I? - You have no idea who I am.
你不知道我有多大能耐
You have no idea what I'm capable of.
彼此彼此
Well, back at you, baby.
让我猜猜看,平衡缆绳上装有炸药
Let me guess. Shaped charge on the counterbalance cable.
主副刹车上应该还有两个
Two more on the primary and secondary brakes.
对吧？
Maybe?
- 他发现了 - 不用你多嘴
- He found them. - Yes. Thank you.
那你知道主缆绳上还有另外一个炸药吗？
Did you also get the base charge at the principal cable?
除非你答应离开，否则我就引爆
Promise to leave town, or I'll blow it.
好吧，我投降
Okay. I give up.
炸吧
Blow it.
- 什么？ - 动手吧，炸吧
- What? - Go on. Blow it.
- 你以为我不会吗？ - 我认为你不会
- You think I won't? - I- I think you won't.
那好
Okay.
5，4 ……
Five, four-
- 有什么遗言吗？- 新窗帘真难看
- Any last words? - The new curtains are hideous.
再见，约翰
Good-bye,John.
- 这是怎么回事儿 - 你说.....再见
- What the hell was that? - You said good-bye.
瓦斯！把瓦斯关掉！
Shut off the gas.!
珍妮
Jane.
女士
Madame.
我有几句话要说
Thought of a number of lines for this moment.
“我只是路过”“嘿，宝贝，谢谢你捅了我一刀”
""Thought I'd just drop in.'' ""Hey, doll. Thanks for givin' me the shaft.''
不错么，你决定什么了
Nice. So, what did you decide?
我想要离婚
I want a divorce.
好啊，当初你在这里向我求婚，现在也算有始有终
I like it.You proposed to me here,so it has agreeable symmetry.
你的衣服，先生？
Coat, sir?
- 我可以坐么？ - 不可以
- May I sit? - No.
- 香槟？ - 不，香槟是庆祝时才喝的
- Champagne, sir? - No. Champagne's for celebrating.
- 给我来杯马蒂尼 - 我什么都不要，谢谢
- I'll have a martini. - I'm fine. Thank you.
我喜欢你的裙子
I like the dress.
我穿的是丧服
I'm in mourning.
你应该多穿穿
You should wear it more often.
你想要什么，约翰？
So, what do you want,John?
珍妮，我们之间出现了不同寻常的问题
We have an unusual problem,Jane.
很明显你希望我死，而我也越来越不为你考虑
You obviously want me dead.And I'm less and less concerned of your well-being.
那我们怎么办？
So, what do we do?
在这里决斗？看谁运气好？
Do we shoot it out here? Hope for the best?
那多难堪
Mm. Well, that would be a shame...
你死了以后他们一定会把我撵出去的
because they would probably ask me to leave once you're dead.
陪我跳个舞
Dance with me.
- 你从不跳舞的 - 那只是掩护的一部分，宝贝
You don't dance.- Just part of my cover,sweetheart.
懒惰也是吗？
Was sloth part of it too?
你说这个故事的结局会是皆大欢喜吗？
You think this story's gonna have a happy ending?
皆大欢喜的只有那些没有结束的故事
Happy endings are just stories that haven't finished yet.
满意了？
Satisfied?
好多年没满足了
Not for years.
那是小约翰 亲爱的
That's all John, sweetheart.
为什么我们的婚姻会失败？
Why is it you think we failed?
因为我们有各自不同的生活？
Because we were leading separate lives?
还是因为我们互相撒谎？
Or was it all the lying that did us in?
我有一个新的理论
I have a theory. Newly formed.
- 洗耳恭听 - 都是你的错
- I'm breathless to hear it.- You killed us.
可笑
Provocative.
你对待婚姻就像对待工作，
You approached our marriage like a job-
先侦查，再计划，然后执行
something to be reconned,planned and executed.
那你做了什么去积极避免婚姻的失败呢？
And you avoided it.
这重要么？我只是你计划的一部分
What do you care,if I was just a cover?
我真的希望你只是计划的一部分
Well, who said you were just a cover?
- 难道我不是么？ - 我不是么？
- Wasn't I? - Well, wasn't I?
我要去……失陪
I have to- Excuse me.
出口不在那边，珍妮
No exits up there,Jane.
保持冷静，约翰，她是个骗子
Be cold,John. She's a liar.
要非常冷静
Be super cold.
来，女士，这边
Come on, honey! This way!
你身上有什么在嘀嗒嘀嗒的叫？
Do you know that you're ticking?
后退，后退！
Get back!Get back! Get back!
坐车么，先生？
Limo, sir?
珍妮·史密斯
Jane Smith.
这是你第二次企图杀我
That's the second time you tried to kill me.
只是个小炸弹而已
Oh, come on.It was just a little bomb.
我这就回家 把所有买给你的东西烧掉
I want you to know. I'm goin'home, and I'm gonna burn everything I ever bought you.
比比看谁快
I'll race you there, baby.
你已经到了么？
You there yet?
我们第一次见面时，你第一感觉是什么？
The first time we met,what was your first thought?
你先说
You tell me.
我……
I thought-
你给我的感觉就像圣诞节的早上
I thought you looked like Christmas morning.
难以形容
I don't know how else to say it.
为什么你现在和我说这个？
And why are you telling me this now?
也许到了故事结尾时才会怀念故事开始的情节
I guess, in the end,you start thinkin' about the beginning.
我只是想让你知道我在想什么
So there it is.I thought you should know.
那你呢，珍妮？
So how about it,Jane? Hmm?
我想……
I thought-
你是我见过的最帅的目标
I thought that you were the most beautiful mark I'd ever seen.
- 这一切都只是桩生意？- 没错
- So it was all business, yeah? - All business.
- 从一开始 - 没错
- From the go.- Cold, hard math.
谢谢，我知道了
Thank you. That's what I needed to know.
好了
Okay.- Okay.
嗨，约翰
Hey,John.
嗨，比尔
Hey, Bill.
- 你没事吧？- 没事
- Uh, are you all right?- Yeah.
好吧
Okay.
顺便说一句，你的车停在人行道上了
Uh, by the way, uh,John, your car is hangin' out over the, uh, sidewalk here.
- 好，谢谢你，比尔 - 晚安
- Yeah. Thanks, Bill.- Okay. Have a good night.
晚安
Good night.
妈的
Shit.
Ow!
你还活着吗，宝贝？
You still alive, baby?
你的枪法和厨艺一样臭，宝贝
Your aim's as bad as your cookin', sweetheart.
那很说明问题
And that's saying something.
来啊，宝贝
Come on, honey.
到爸爸这儿来
Come to daddy.
现在谁是你爸爸？
Who's your daddy now?
我下不了手
I can't do it.
来啊，开枪啊
Don't! Come on!
来啊！
Come on!
你想吗？
You want it?
开枪吧
It's yours.
哦 我不能..
Oh, I can't-
来吧
Come on. Mmm.
你好，陌生人
Hiya, stranger.
我回来了
Hiya back.
- 你好？- 没发生什么事吧？我们听到很大的动静
- Yeah?-  Is everything okay? We heard an awful ruckus.
- 没事儿，一切都很好 这些人是... - 你们一切都好？
No. Everything's fine here.Yeah. It's great.So you guys are - You're fine?
好得不能再好了
Yeah. Couldn't be better.
哦 很好 你们…… 但是...
Oh. Nice.You guys- But are-
- 苏希，马丁- 晚安
- Suzy. Martin. Officers.- Have a nice night.
你们在重新装修啊，那真是
Looks like you're redecorating. It's very-
是的 可惜那些红橡木地板
Yeah. Shame about the teak.
- 你的左勾拳很厉害嘛- 你防守得也不错
That left of yours.A thing ofbeauty.- You take it well.
谢谢
Thank you.
在阿斯彭的那个假期 - 嗯
- That vacation in Aspen- - Mm.
你提前走了，为什么？
You left early. Why?
- 吉恩·鲁克·加斯帕德 - 喔，上帝啊
-Jean-Luc Gaspard.- Oh! God!  Oh.
- 呵呵 - 我也想杀他
- Yeah.- I wanted him.
算了
- Forget it.- Wow.
那次我们结婚周年，我坐直升机回来的，你没有听到么?
You didn't hear me that night the chopper dropped me off for our anniversary dinner?
- 没有- 为什么？
- No.- No?
手榴弹炸的，我那晚耳朵有点聋
Mm. Percussion grenades.I was partially deaf that night.
我有点色盲
- I'm slightly color blind.- Mm.
- 视网膜有点受损- 我这三个手指没有知觉
- Retinal scarring.- I can't feel anything in these three fingers.
三根肋骨(断过)，眼框破裂
- Three ribs. Broken eye socket.- Mm. Oh.
耳膜穿孔
Perforated eardrum. Mm.
你每次行动后会睡不着么？
You ever have trouble sleeping after?
- 不会- 我也不会
- Nope.- Yeah. Me neither.
快！当心！
Go, go, go, go, go!Look out!
走
Move.
鞋子
Shoes.
他们限我48小时杀了你
I was given 48 hours to take you out.
我也一样
Same.
天哪，信任都哪儿去了？
Jesus. Where's the trust?
你还想怎么样？
What do you expect?
你怎么给我一把女人枪？
Why do I get the girl gun?
- 你开玩笑吗？- 没有
- Are you kiddin' me?- No.
谢谢
Thank you.
注意 他们出来了
Come on.! They're outside.!
科尔曼家
Colemans.
他们借的烧烤工具好几个月没还了
Guy's had my barbecue set for months.
我从没参加过和平队
I was never in the Peace Corps.
什么？我以前很喜欢你那一点
What? No.I really liked that about you.
呃 太诚实也许不是好主意
- Well, maybe this honesty thing isn't such a good idea.
- 我没上过麻省理工学院 - 真的？
- I didn't go to M.I.T.- Really?
巴黎圣母院，我主修艺术历史
Notre Dame.Art history major.
- 艺术？- 历史
- Art?- History.
- 那里很有名- 好吧
- It's reputable.- Okay.
现在干这行的越来越年轻
Fuckers get younger every year.
我必须告诉你，我从来没喜欢过你的厨艺
I have to tell you.I never really liked your cooking.
-
- Hmm.
不是你的特长
It's not your gift.
我这辈子从来没做过饭
Baby, I've never cooked a day in my life.
都是我的属下做的
I-Temp girls cooked.
全是谎言！
Web of lies!
我喜欢这首歌
I like it. Deal with it.
- 有追兵- 什么？
- We got company.- What?
他妈的！
Shit.
- 亲爱的 把车开稳点 - 这是专业的甩脱跟踪式开法 宝贝
- Baby, hold steady. Now!- It's called evasive driving, sweetheart.
开稳
Hold still!
装了这么多乱七八糟的东西，让我怎么开
This thing's all over the place.How do you drive these things anyways?
宝贝
Honey!
什么乱七八糟的
- Transmission's terrible.
- 我来开吧- 我能行
- Honey, let me drive.- I got it.
让开
Move over. Move.
我是家庭主妇(车是家庭型的车)
I'm the suburban housewife,sweetheart.
- 快让我- 好吧
- You move.- Fine. Go.
- 来- 好了
- Go.- Go.
是防弹的！
They're bulletproof.
有件事儿，我想告诉你
You know, honey,I should probably tell you.
我曾经结过一次婚
I was married once before.
你疯了么 你怎么了？
Are you out of your mind? What is wrong with you?
问你自己！
You're what's wrong with me.
- 那次只是在维加斯喝多了- 好啊，更好了，太好了
- It was a drunken Vegas thing!- Oh, that's better!That's much better. That's great.
够了
Stop it.
快开！
Go, go, go!
她的名字和社会福利号码是多少？
What's her name and Social Security number?
不 你不能杀她
No. You're not gonna kill her.
这门还真有用
These doors are handy.
亲爱的，你也有点伪善
You know, sweetheart,you're being a bit hypocritical.
你不也是什么纯情少女
It's not like you're some beacon of truth.
约翰，我父母……
John, my parents-
在我5岁的时候就过世了，我是个孤儿
They died when I was five.I'm an orphan.
那我们婚礼上你的爸爸是谁？
Who-Who was that kindly fella who gave you away at our wedding?
雇的演员
Paid actor.
我就说么，我好像在电视上看到你爸
I said- I said I saw your dad on Fantasy Island.!
我知道
I know.
我不想谈那个
You know, I don't even want to talk about it.
- 你瞄准了吗？- 瞄准了
- You got it? - Got it.
- 你慢慢瞄 (讽刺) - 瞄准了
- Any time. - I got 'em.
我们必须把以前说过的话重新老实地说一遍
We're gonna have to redo every conversation we've ever had.
我是犹太人
I'm Jewish.
我真笨，我带了我真正的父母去参加婚礼
I can't believe I brought my real parents to our wedding.
真恶心，这也能端上来
Disgusting. How could you serve this to someone?
小姐，能不能把这个重新热一下？
Excuse me, ma'am.Is it possible to get this reheated? Miss?
小姐，我跟你说话呢
Miss, I'm talkin' to you. Excuse me.
上帝啊，约翰
-Jesus,Johnny.
- 早上好，埃迪 - 早上好
- Good morning, Eddie - Morning.
真高兴见到你没事
It's good to see you're okay, man.
你一定回心转意，把那个满嘴胡话的婊子给杀了
Tell me you got smart and that you killed that lyin' bitch.
我这个满嘴胡话的婊子？
Hmm. This lying bitch?
只是希望而已
Guess it was just wishful thinking.
- 对不起 - 埃迪
- I'm sorry. -  Eddie, we got...
- 见到你很高兴，珍妮 - 埃迪，听我说
- It's nice to see you,Jane. - Eddie. Eddie, focus, please.
- 我们有麻烦了 - 麻烦？
- We got problems. - You got problems?
吸毒的人才有麻烦，你们俩是死定了
Crack addicts got problems, my friend. You two are smoked.
- 也许是的- 也许？
- Maybe.- Maybe?
整个杀手公司都在找你，
John, you got the entire agency gunnin' for you.
也许她的公司也是
Probably have her agency gunnin' for you too.
那你呢
What about you?
- 我？ - 你站哪边？
- Me? - Where are you at?
我站哪一边？
Where am I at?
我今天早上刚刚拒绝了一桩生意
I find myself dragging my feet this morning.
我想你欠我一笔钱
I think you owe me a little money anyway.
- 那你…… - 女士，我知道我们互相不了解
- What do you think? - We don't understand each other.And I understand that.
但你也不要用那种眼光看着我，好吗？我和他认识好久了
But I don't need those looks from you. I've been in his life a long time.
- 听我说，埃迪 - 很久了
- Eddie, Eddie. Focus. Focus. - I've been in his life for a long time.
他们把我房子炸了，还向我的老婆开枪，我自己的公司！
I'm pissed off. They blew up my house. They shot at my wife. My own company.
如果她的工作如她所说的是电脑公司
If she works for who the street...says that she works for...
那你就是“梅希&金贝尔”公司，如果她是为WE频道工作，那你就是……
you're Macy's and Gimbel's.She would be the WE channel,and you would be...
为某个和WE频道竞争的频道工作
whatever channel it is that competes against the WE channel.
知道我说什么吗 明白我的意思么 - 嗯
- Know what I'm saying? You following me? - Mm-hmm.
道理很简单，一旦你们俩被除名
Johnny, the point is simple. Once you guys decide to get off the reservation, that's it.
- 你们就永远被除名了(还要被灭口)- 埃迪，情况有多坏？
- Then you're off the reservation.- Eddie, how bad?
有多坏？
- How bad is it? - Mm.
你记得加拿大那次吗？
You remember Canada.
- 跟你们比是小儿科
That was kid stuff next to what you're up against.
- 那是你杀的？管你什么事儿？
- That was you? - Oh, is that a turn-on?
她是不是想用车撞死你？
- She tried to kill you with a car.
这又不是我的主意 - 够了
Not my business. - Stop.
我不多嘴了，可这是事实
A good friend stays out of it.I understand. This is the facts.
这么说吧，如果你们二人分开，还有一线希望
If you two separate from each other, you got a shot.
不是什么好主意 约翰 但是你还有机会
Not a great shot,Johnny,but you got a shot.
如果你们还在一起，只有死路一条！
You two stay together,you're dead.
除非你们可以找到什么比你们更让他们感兴趣的东西
Unless you can find something that they want more than they want you.
找到他了，他被关在政府大楼的地下二层的D区
Found him. He's being held in subbasement ""D'' of the federal courthouse.
戒备森严，有监视器和热感应器，电源直接来自市电站
High security.Motion and thermal.Power's on a city grid.
我只能帮你这些了，珍妮
This is as far as we go,Jane.
- 那好，谢谢- 祝你走运，宝贝
- Right. Thanks for everything.- Good luck, babe.
有一股西北风
We have this northwesterly flow...
穿越中部地区
coming down through the middle of the country.
所以我们可以看到在这一片区域...
So we're seeing successive areas...
你们可以换一下台吗？
Do one of you guys mind changing the channel?
尼克，你能不能抬抬你那个大屁股，给我换一下台
Nick.Would you please get off your fat ass and change the channel?
我知道这很难，谢谢了
I know. It's tough.Thank you.
未来温度可能会持续下降
That's going to make things even colder than they are right now.
你们走吧
You guys go.
我们有30秒时间，，我切断电源，你带人走
Thirty-second window.I cut the power,you grab the kid.
很简单 明白了么 - 明白
Simple and clean. Got it? - Got it.
告诉我，你一共杀过多少人？
So tell me. How many?
和这有关系吗？
Does it matter?
- 我先说好了 - 好啊
- Should I go first? - Okay.
我记不太清了……不过
I don't exactly keep count, but
大概有……
I would say...
50到60个 - 嗯
- high 50s, low 60s.- Mm-hmm.
我从不松懈，不过最重要的还是……
Been around the block, but...you know, the important thing is
312个
312个？
31 2?
- 怎么可能？- 有时一次两个
- How?- Some were two at a time.
- 宝贝？- 别说了……
- Honey.- I'm- I'm- I'm-
找到他了
Baby's in the crib.
你把看热闹的也算进去了？
Are you counting innocent bystanders?
- 你在监视着周围么？- 周围都查过了
- Monitoring the perimeter?- I checked the perimeter.
- 警察的频率呢？- 正在监听
- What about the police bands?- I am on the police bands.
- 保持连接 - 我又不是新手
- Connected to the main - This is not my first time.
为了确保成功
I think we've established that.
好吧
All right.
向左转
Turn left.
向左转，约翰
Left,John.
向左转
Left!
你不能和蔼一点么？别这么对我说话好吗
Be nice.You don't have to talk to me like that. Okay?
- 请左转 - 我不能向左转
Left, please? - I can't go left. You see?
左边没路 看见了么
There is no left. Look.
要么向前，要么回去
I have straight.I have back the way I came.
左边没路，你要我向哪走？
There's no left.Which way do you want me to go?
- 等我的信号- 看到这儿都是水么？
-Just stay there and wait for my mark.- See what I'm sitting in?
看到么？
See that?
- 慢慢来 - 行了，待着别动
- Take your time.- Yeah. All right. Stay.
待着别动 等我的信号，马上就好了
Stay there.Wait for my mark. I'll find it.
等我的信号
Wait for my mark.
马上就好了，不知道是怎么回事，等一下
Almost there.I don't know what happened.Just hold on.
约翰，你在干什么呢？
What are you-John, what are you doing?What are you doing?
我给你信号，你就切断照明
Kill the lights on my signal.
切！
Now. Kill the lights.
- 珍妮，切断电源！ - 那是什么？
Jane, kill the lights.- Hey. Who's that?
- 哪儿？- 把灯开开！笨蛋！
- Where? - No, no. Not now! Turn 'em back on!
笨蛋
- Idiot!
- 他们来了- 给我打开手铐
- Here they come.- Hey, Nick. Uncuff me.
把灯打开，把灯打开！
Turn 'em on!Turn 'em back on!
- 把灯打开！- 好
- Turn it back on.- All right.
- 开灯！ - 闭嘴！
Give me light. Shut up. Shut up. Shut up.
- 尼克！- 闭嘴！
- Nick.- Shut up.
给我一把枪，尼克，给我一把枪！
Give me a gun.Nick, give me a gun.
快开门！
Open the door.
快开门
open the door
后门
Back there.
小心点，快进来
Look out.Move, move, move.
这是个老谋深算的家伙
This guy's a wily one.
关门
Shut the door.
快，快，另一条路
Move. Move. The other way.
这玩意是怎么弄的
How's this work?
我告诉你要等我的信号
I told you to wait for my signal.
- 你没有等我的信号 - 是的，我随机应变了
- You didn't wait for my signal. - Well, I improvised.
- 你把整个计划打乱了 - 你的计划有问题
- You deviated from the plan. - The plan was flawed.
- 我的计划没有问题 - 死心眼儿
- The plan was not flawed. - Anal.
- 这叫有组织，有纪律 - 珍妮，90%的时候要靠本能
- Organized. -Jane, 90% of this job is instinct.
你的本能把报警器都搞响了
Your instincts set off every alarm in the building.
但任务完成了，虽然不是珍妮式的
My instincts got the job done.May not have been theJane show.
不是，这是约翰式的，就像那次圣诞节，我们的结婚周年纪念
No. It was theJohn show. It was half-assed.Like Christmas. Like our anniversary.
还有那次你忘了给我妈买生日礼物
Like the time you forgot to bring my mother's birthday present.
你假妈的生日！
Your fake mother's birthday.
问题是 你总是第一个脱离团队的
The point is, you are always the first to break team.
你不需要团队，只是想要几个给你打杂的仆人
You don't want a team. You-You want a servant for hire.
我想要个靠得住的人
I want someone I can count on.
珍妮，你太咄咄逼人了
Jane, there's no air around you anymore.
你说这话什么意思？
Okay. What is that supposed to mean?
我是说你容不得一丝错误，不容自由发挥
It means there's no room for mistakes. No mistakes whatsoever.
我的意思 这谁能受得了？
No spontaneity. I mean, who can answer to that?
你完全可以不这么做
Well, you don't have to. Do you?
因为这根本不是真正的婚姻
'Cause this isn't even a real marriage.
- 你们到底是谁？- 闭嘴！
-  Who are you people?- Shut up!
你现在见证了
So, now I realize...
我和我老婆有些家庭纠纷
you witnessed the missus and I working through some domestic issues.
哦
Oh
甚为遗憾
That's regrettable.
但是别以为我们会手软，这样想就错了
But don't take that as a sign of weakness.That would be a mistake on your part.
告诉我们，你知道什么
Now tell us what you know.
为什么我们两个的老板都希望你死
Why do both our bosses want you dead?
你....
You unders-
宝贝，拜托
Honey, please.
好吧
Wrap it up.
在人质面前也要给我留点面子吧
Maybe it's not such a good idea to undermine me in front of the hostage.
会给人错误的印象
Sends a mixed message.
对不起
Sorry.
女人就是这样
Girls.
好了，问到哪儿了？
Okay.  Where was I?
- 是你的错 - 闭嘴，听着
-""A mistake on your part." - Shut up. Options.
下面我要给你几条路走，A……
I'm gonna lay out your options for you.Okay? Option "A. '"
我能不能...
If I could
闭嘴
Shut up.
A，我们问，你回答，没有痛苦
Option "A. '" You talk. We listen.No pain.
B，如果你不说
Option ""B.''You don't talk.
我会用钳子把你大拇指拔掉，会很疼的
I remove your thumbs with my pliers.It will hurt.
选项C
Option ""C.''
我会换一些花样，不过最终的结局都是你死
I like to vary the details a bit,but the punch line is you die.
- 本杰明 - 好的
- Benjamin. - Okay.
我们不是很有耐心的人
We're impatient people.
能给我来杯汽水吗？果汁也行
Can I get a soda? Or a juice or, uh, some-
A！A！我选A！
""A.'' ""A.'' Option ""A.'' Aaah!
- 好痛啊- 打得好
- Oh, that hurt.- Okay. That was a nice shot.
你吓得哆嗦了么？
What's-You got a spasm?
我动不了，你们自己看我裤兜里的东西
I'm tied up.Why don't you check my back pocket?
我不是目标，你们才是 你们俩
I'm not the target. You are.Both of you
他们知道你们结婚了
They found out you're married...
所以让你们去杀同一个目标
so they teamed up and sent youto the same hit to target each other.
这是你们两个公司合作的计划
It was a joint task force by both your companies.
两个互相竞争的杀手住在同一屋檐下，这不是什么好事
Two competing agents living under the same roof.It's bad for business.
- 他们想你们自相残杀 - 你是个诱饵
- They wanted you to take each other out.- You were bait.
我才来公司，初级员工
Well, it's entry level.Toehold into the company.
给我这么重要的任务，其实很不错
Couple hits,they bump me up to a desk.It's pretty cool actually.
你把照片放在口袋里干什么？
You keep the photo in your back pocket?
难道还要我去配个镜框？
What was I supposed to do? Frame it?
应该毁掉，烧掉
You get rid of it. You burn it.
这是第101条守则 可能我没看到这一条
- Tradecraft 1 01 .- I'm sorry. I guess I skipped that day.
不过你们可能也没看到不能和敌人结婚这一条
Just like I guess you skipped the day about not marrying the enemy.
你现在仍然是诱饵么？
You were bait,or you are bait?
腰带！腰带，老兄
Belt. Belt. Belt, dude.
2分钟
Two minutes.
1分钟
One minute.
帮帮我啊
A little help.
安全
Clear.
嘿，我想我撞坏我的牙了，我们这有牙医吗？
Hey, I think I chipped my tooth.Do you know if we have dental?
我外逃的船停在拉巴斯
My way out is a boat standing by in La Paz.
我的在阿特拉斯山脉，说这个干嘛？
Cargo drop, Atlas Mountains. So what?
这样我们即使分开也能找到对方
So, at least, apart, we know what the odds are.
这一次
Let's just call this what it is...
我们只能听天由命了
and what it isn't.
为什么我们的婚姻这么糟糕？
All right. So it's a crap marriage.
我们天生就是冤家对头
All right. I'm a mess.You're a disaster.
我们俩都是骗子
We're both liars.
但是如果你逃走，你一生都只能逃亡
But you run,you'll always be running.
我说咱们留下来，战斗到底
I say we stay and we fight.
把这一切解决
We finish this thing.
到时，如果你想走，我不拦你
Then if you wanna go,you can go.
谢谢
Oh, thank you.
说什么“听天由命”，真是的
What? ""Let's call this what it is.''Jesus Christ.
- 住手……- 别动
- Stop.- Don't.
哦，天呐
Oh,Jesus.
这家店真不错
This is a really good store.
- 珍妮，下辈子再见- 你也一样
- See you in the next life,Jane.- Likewise,John.
哦
Oh.
对不起
Sorry.
回去和你算帐
We'll talk about this later.
上帝啊！
Jesus!
- 不是我碰的 - 就是你
- I didn't touch a thing.- Yes, you did.
- 对不起，那把刀…… - 我不想谈
- Sorry about the, uh, knife in- - I don't want to talk about it.
- 我负责狙击 - 我来当诱饵
- I'll fly. - I'll be bait.
我顺时针移动，帮我看着背后 - 好的
- I'm goin' clockwise, so watch my 6:00. - All right.
走！
Go! Move!
情况怎么样？
How's it look?
小菜一碟
It's a piece of cake.
小心点
Watch these.
他们都疯了 小心点
They tend to jam. So watch 'em.
你喜欢左边了，那我就打右边
You favor your left, sweetheart,so look out for right.
现在想想，拉巴斯的那条船肯定很不错
Damn. That boat in La Paz is lookin'pretty good right now, isn't it?
这个时候那边应该是雨季
Well, it rains a lot this time of year.
闭嘴
Shut up.
我对你们这几个星期的进步很感兴趣
I'm interested in the progress you've made in the last few weeks.
我们还可以吧, 但说实话，我的意思是..你知道...
Uh, doin' all right, aren't we? I mean, listen.I'm not gonna lie to you.
有时候，我真的想……
There were times I just wanted to-
- 杀了她, 但是……- 我也一样
- kill her, but, uh - Likewise.
- 下不了手 - 那是好事儿啊
couldn't take the shot.- That's a good sign.
- 谁能想到呢？ - 有时候你们必须努力去克服困难
- Who would've thought.- Sometimes you have to battle through.
- 那就是婚姻，不是吗？- 对，只要我们努力……
- That's marriage, right?- Yeah. You take your best shot and-
- 我们重新装修了房子
- Oh. We redid the house.
- 是啊，没错
We did. Yes, we did.
生活中总会有这样那样的困难和威胁
You know, there will always be challenges.Threats out there.
对
Yep.
你们只要齐心协力就可以克服
But you can handle it together.
- 至少现在 - 是的，我们可以……至少现在？
- So far.- Yes, we ca- So far?
这是什么意思？
Oh, what is that?
- 将来是什么样很难说啊 - 至少现在……
I'm leaving room for the unknown. So far.
而且你们是不是感觉到现在的关系会更有利于……
And do you feel that your relationship styles... are more conducive to the free flow-
你倒是问那个有关性的问题啊
Ask us the sex question.
约翰
John.
啊…… 好吧 那么.... - 十分
- Uh, well, that...  - Ten.
-=The Last Fantasy=-
荣誉出品，谢谢观赏